/lykola Maslakai

Front-End Developer(React)

Ukraine, Khmelnytskyi 0992620229| nikolaymaslakay@gmail.com| Linkedin | Github

Summary

I'm an ambitious and goal-oriented Junior Front - End Developer with more 1 year of experience in full-stack development of complex web services. My project experience includes both team and individual projects. I'm attentive to details and have good analytical skills what allows me to learn new information quickly. Beyond coding, I am constantly improving myself by learning new technologies and improving my skillset.

Skills

Programming Javascript, Typescript

Frameworks React, React Native, Redux, Next, Node.js, Express, REST API

Databases PostgreSQL, MongoDB, SQL Server

Languages

English: Intermediate Ukraine: Native

Experience

Team Challenge

Front-end developer • Development and support of the user interface of the marketplace. Jan. 2024 - Present

Interaction with designers and back-end developers to ensure optimal functionality.

• Implement new features and improve existing code.

• Optimize page loading speed and support for responsive design.

Freelancehunt.com Khmelnytsky, Ukraine

Full-stack developer

Development in Javascript(TypeScript) and NodeJS.

· Work and negotiations with clients.

Feb. 2023 - Present • Work on projects of various sizes and complexity.

Project

Marketplace Peach (volunteer team project)

TS, JS, React, ReduxToolkit, Tailwind CSS, Node.js

Github Demo

Role: Front-End dev.

Khmelnvtskv, Ukraine

Peach is an online platform designed to facilitate the buying and selling of goods among users. It provides a secure environment for sellers and buyers, allowing them to easily interact and conduct transactions.

The goal of Peach is to create a convenient and reliable platform where users can exchange goods, explore new offers, and make purchases with maximum confidence.

Marketplace-Sviy (volunteer team project)

TS, JS, React, Next.js, ReduxToolkit, Tailwind CSS

Role: Front-End dev. Github Demo

Marketplace-Sviy is an online platform designed to support Ukrainian manufacturers who want to introduce and sell their products through the Internet. In this market, manufacturers can post information about their products, including photographs, descriptions and prices. In addition, the platform provides safe and convenient payment and delivery methods so that buyers can make purchases with confidence and comfort.

Role: Full-Stack dev. Netflixtube

TS, React, Next.js, Mongodb

"Netflixtube" is a web application created based on the design of the Netflix service. This application allows for the viewing of a large number of movies. Here are some features: the application implements a verification system that allows users to create their own accounts for storing personal settings and movie lists, verification using Google and Github: Users can use their Google or Github accounts to log into the application, providing an additional level of convenience and security, adding movies to favorites: Users can add movies to their favorites, allowing them to easily return to them later.

Education

Genius.space

Full-Stack Developer | Front-end Developer

Kyiv, Ukraine Jun. 2023 - Jan. 2024

Odessa. Ukraine

Odesa Polytechnic National University University Degree | Road transport in the economy

Sep. 2015 - Jul. 2019